<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>For Future Reference</title>
    <link>https://potocnyj.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on For Future Reference</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/potocnyj&#34;&gt;John Potocny&lt;/a&gt; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 13:25:54 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://potocnyj.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Get More Value Out of 1:1 Meetings - Set an Agenda</title>
      <link>https://potocnyj.github.io/posts/getting-more-value-out-of-one-on-ones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 13:25:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://potocnyj.github.io/posts/getting-more-value-out-of-one-on-ones/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking recently about how to get more value of 1:1 meetings with my manager. Over time I got into the bad habit of treating 1:1s like a personalized status update; just talking about what I&amp;rsquo;m working on and any potential impediments. I&amp;rsquo;m giving a lot more thought now to what I want out of my career and how to improve my performance outside of the quality of my code, and the first thing I&amp;rsquo;m trying to fix is approaching 1:1s as a meeting for me, and not an extension of daily standups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Higher Standard for Filing Issues</title>
      <link>https://potocnyj.github.io/posts/a-higher-standard-for-filing-issues/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 16:46:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://potocnyj.github.io/posts/a-higher-standard-for-filing-issues/</guid>
      <description>Last Friday, a couple of my colleagues were cleaning up old issues in Github, and I decided to go through the issues I had filed and close out all of the ones that I didn&amp;rsquo;t think made sense to keep. I started with 178 open issues authored by me; at the end I had only 12.
Of the issues I closed, some were outdated, no longer relevant, or superseded by other planned work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a Blog</title>
      <link>https://potocnyj.github.io/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 14:19:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://potocnyj.github.io/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve tried starting a blog a couple of times before, using platforms like Google Blogs or Wordpress. Every time before I would write maybe a couple of posts, then get bored or forget about it and stop writing. I&amp;rsquo;m trying again, using my own static site this time. The goal this time is to give myself a place to record thoughts while also hopefully also learning a little bit about making a static site (since I&amp;rsquo;ve always been strictly a backend developer).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>